<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FREE ROBUX</string>
    <string name="agreement">ITCLUB built the [free vbucksr] app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by ITCLUB at no cost and is intended for use as is.

This page is used to inform website visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.

If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at [free vbucksr] unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

we are not affiliated with any Fornite or Any brand.

Information Collection and Use

For a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that I request is retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way

The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.

Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app

Google Play Services
AdMob
Log Data

I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.

Cookies

Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device\'s internal memory.

This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.

Service Providers

I may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

To facilitate our Service;
To provide the Service on our behalf;
To perform Service-related services; or
To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
I want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.

Security

I value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and I cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Links to Other Sites

This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

Children’s Privacy

These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. I do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the case I discover that a child under 13 has provided me with personal information, I immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to do necessary actions.

Changes to This Privacy Policy

I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me.</string>
    <string name="game_guide">Kids register for Roblox with their birth date. It’s important for kids to enter their correct birth date because Roblox has default security and privacy settings that vary, based on a player’s age.
You can check the age bracket of your child’s account by looking in the upper-right corner of the navigation bar, where it will read “13+” or less then 13,” depending on the date of birth given when the account was opened. If your child has previously set up an account incorrectly with an age of 13+, it’s simple to change the child’s age to less then 13 in the account settings section.
All Roblox games feature basic security and privacy measures. All user-uploaded images are reviewed by human moderators for inappropriate content before being posted, and there are filters that weed out bad words and other problematic language. Players age 13 and older can see and say more words and phrases than younger players, but inappropriate chat and sharing personal information (including phone numbers and addresses) are restricted regardless of age. Links to YouTube channels and social media usernames can be shared by players 13 and older.  While the imagery on Roblox has a blocky, digitized look, parents should be aware that some of the user-generated games on Roblox may include themes and/or imagery that may be too intense for young or sensitive players.</string>


    <string name="squad_team">How to Play Squads and Duos in Fortnite Battle Royale
To play as a pair or a squad of up to four, start up Fortnite Battle Royale as usual -- until you reach the gameplay menu. You\'ll then cycle through the available modes to find the Duo and Squad options using Square (PS4), X (Xbox One), or the keypad (PC) depending on the platform you’re playing on. From there, you can invite friends to play with you or you can auto-fill the slots with random players.
To invite your friends into Duos and Squads, select the empty slot and scroll through your friends list to send them an invite. In Fortnite Battle Royale, the Squad, Duo, and normal modes are separated so you can’t steamroll lone players as a group of four.
Why Play as a Squad or Duo?
Obviously, it benefits you to have another set of eyes (or three) watching your back while you're looting an area. It also helps that your teammates can revive you if you need it. </string>


    <string name="tips">They say the best things in life are free and that mostly applies to the life of a Roblox player as well. All of the best games are free-to-play without any major strings attached and you aren’t required to spend any real money to enjoy most of the content on Roblox. But if you do want to drop a few bucks here and there or subscribe to The Builders Club, you’re gonna need to know what Robux are and how they work.

Just like you need cash in real life to buy things and get by, most people are going to need some Robux to enjoy Roblox to the fullest. While the vast majority of Roblox can be accessed without spending any real money on Robux at all, there are some aspects of the game that you need Robux to see and other parts that are enhanced by the use of Robux.</string>


    <string name="tricks">How Do Robux Work?
Think of Robux as like a new type of currency. When you visit another country you’ve got to transfer your funds to the local currency, such as dollars to pounds when going from the US to the UK, and Robux are the same — except you’re swapping your dollars for Robux. It’s just a digital currency. Although, much like Monopoly money, Robux don’t have any real cash value in and of themselves.
At any time during Roblox you can visit the Buy Robux page to make a direct purchase. Spending $4.95 will grant you 400 Robux (R$) and spending $9.95 will grant you R$800. Naturally, the more you spend the better the value is. It goes all the way up to R$22,500 for $199.95.

Using Robux you can purchase limited time exclusive items, like these Sparkling Angel Wings, for your character to wear. You can also purchase Game Passes that grant in-game bonuses such as extra storage or a bigger duffel bag in the GTA-style game, Jailbreak. Then going a step even further, some games aren’t free to access like others and actually require you to spend Robux just to play the game at all, such as Welcome to Bloxburg, which costs R$25.
A lot of players put a lot of stock into how many Robux they have, sort of like a status symbol. This often leads to players feeling desperate, as if they need to find ways to get more Robux easily so that they can keep up with others. Just remember that almost everything in Roblox is free and you can have fun without ever spending money.
Avoiding Robux Scams
That being said, it’s true that Robux are what make the world of Roblox go round. And because they’re so valuable and important a lot of people will try and trick you with scams. If you ever see anything claiming to be giving out free Robux just for playing the game or if someone asks you for your information in exchange for Robux, it’s a scam and you shouldn’t trust it.

For more detailed information about avoiding Robux scams in Roblox, we’ve got you covered. Be careful out there!</string>


    <string name="vbucks">Bangladesh Railway will start selling advance train tickets on August 8 for Eid-ul-Azha travel, reports UNB. At a Dhaka Railway Bhaban press briefing on Thursday, Railways Minister Mazibul Hoque said tickets for travel on August 17, 18, 19, 20 and 21 will be available on August 8, 9, 10, 11 and 12 respectively. Tickets for the Eid-ul-Azha holiday return journeys on August 24, 25,26,27 and 28, will be available on August 15 16, 17, 18 and 19, he said. Ticket sales will begin at 8am and each passenger will be able to buy a maximum of four tickets. Nine sets of special trains for inbound and outbound travel will run on various routes on the occasion of Eid</string>
    <string name="vbucks_title">VBucks</string>
    <string name="tricks_title">Tricks</string>
    <string name="tips_title">Tips</string>
    <string name="squad_team_title">Squad and Team</string>
    <string name="game_guide_title">Robux Guide</string>
</resources>
