<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FREE V-BUCKS</string>
    <string name="agreement">ITCLUB built the [free vbucksr] app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by ITCLUB at no cost and is intended for use as is.

This page is used to inform website visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.

If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at [free vbucksr] unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

we are not affiliated with any Fornite or Any brand.

Information Collection and Use

For a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that I request is retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way

The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.

Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app

Google Play Services
AdMob
Log Data

I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.

Cookies

Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device\'s internal memory.

This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.

Service Providers

I may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

To facilitate our Service;
To provide the Service on our behalf;
To perform Service-related services; or
To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
I want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.

Security

I value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and I cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Links to Other Sites

This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

Children’s Privacy

These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. I do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the case I discover that a child under 13 has provided me with personal information, I immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to do necessary actions.

Changes to This Privacy Policy

I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me.</string>
    <string name="game_guide">Bangladesh Railway will start selling advance train tickets on August 8 for Eid-ul-Azha travel, reports UNB. At a Dhaka Railway Bhaban press briefing on Thursday, Railways Minister Mazibul Hoque said tickets for travel on August 17, 18, 19, 20 and 21 will be available on August 8, 9, 10, 11 and 12 respectively. Tickets for the Eid-ul-Azha holiday return journeys on August 24, 25,26,27 and 28, will be available on August 15 16, 17, 18 and 19, he said. Ticket sales will begin at 8am and each passenger will be able to buy a maximum of four tickets. Nine sets of special trains for inbound and outbound travel will run on various routes on the occasion of Eid</string>
    <string name="squad_team">How to Play Squads and Duos in Fortnite Battle Royale
To play as a pair or a squad of up to four, start up Fortnite Battle Royale as usual -- until you reach the gameplay menu. You\'ll then cycle through the available modes to find the Duo and Squad options using Square (PS4), X (Xbox One), or the keypad (PC) depending on the platform you’re playing on. From there, you can invite friends to play with you or you can auto-fill the slots with random players.
To invite your friends into Duos and Squads, select the empty slot and scroll through your friends list to send them an invite. In Fortnite Battle Royale, the Squad, Duo, and normal modes are separated so you can’t steamroll lone players as a group of four.
Why Play as a Squad or Duo?
Obviously, it benefits you to have another set of eyes (or three) watching your back while you're looting an area. It also helps that your teammates can revive you if you need it. </string>
    <string name="tips">Pro Tip: In Duo mode, if you down a player, don\'t finish them off immediately. Lie in wait for their partner to come and revive your bait to try and finish off the Duo.
Because the different modes are separated, you’ll either only be playing against other Duos or other Squads. This means that you can play with friends while remaining on a level playing field with the opposition.
Although Squads can be made up of less than four players by not auto-filling the remaining slots, doing so immediately puts your team at a disadvantage. Unless you’re looking for a challenge, I wouldn’t recommend playing Squads without a full team of four players.
But the main reason why you want to play as a Duo or Squad in Fortnite is because it just makes the game more fun. Playing with friends in video games like this always creates wonderful, shared moments that remind us why video games are so great.</string>
    <string name="tricks">Do NOT get caught in the storm
The other first rule of Fortnite: do not mess with The Storm. It\'s a beast of a thing that can\'t be controlled. It is your biggest enemy, even scarier than the 99 others standing between you and Victory Royale.
This is especially true as you get closer to the top 10, as the safe zone gets smaller and the storm hits much harder. Run away from it, always.
Shoot first, loot later
As you\'re out there looking for the items and tools to help you to victory, don\'t forget that those tools won\'t do you any good if you\'re dead. When you\'re coming to a new area, take time to scope it out and see if anyone is lingering around before you start putting your head inside loot crates.
Don\'t be one dimensional
You know how you\'re never supposed to bring a knife to a gunfight? Well, the same thing is sort of true in Fortnite: you never want to go into battle without a balanced loadout that will help you adapt to changing conditions. Just as you wouldn\'t want to use a sniper in close quarters, you wouldn't want a shotgun up against someone who can land accurate shots from hundreds of meters out.
An example of a well-balanced loadout is a shotgun, an assault rifle, and a sniper rifle, with the other 2 slots of your inventory taking up healing items. You don't always have to go this route (in fact, as you play more you'll find that this is harder to achieve than you think), but the idea is to be able to protect yourself the most you can from any distance.
Use your surroundings to track enemy players
If you picked up some tracking skills in the Boy or Girl Scouts, it's time to put them to use here. Due to the nature of how people build in Fortnite, you will come across structures abandoned in the world for one reason or another. These structures may be one ramp or a mile-high fortress, but either way, you'll want to take note of where they are and how certain elements are positioned.</string>
    <string name="vbucks">Bangladesh Railway will start selling advance train tickets on August 8 for Eid-ul-Azha travel, reports UNB. At a Dhaka Railway Bhaban press briefing on Thursday, Railways Minister Mazibul Hoque said tickets for travel on August 17, 18, 19, 20 and 21 will be available on August 8, 9, 10, 11 and 12 respectively. Tickets for the Eid-ul-Azha holiday return journeys on August 24, 25,26,27 and 28, will be available on August 15 16, 17, 18 and 19, he said. Ticket sales will begin at 8am and each passenger will be able to buy a maximum of four tickets. Nine sets of special trains for inbound and outbound travel will run on various routes on the occasion of Eid</string>
    <string name="vbucks_title">VBucks</string>
    <string name="tricks_title">Tricks</string>
    <string name="tips_title">Tips</string>
    <string name="squad_team_title">Squad and Team</string>
    <string name="game_guide_title">Game Guide</string>
</resources>
