<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tactic Top For CR</string>
    <string name="agreement">This Application collects some Personal Data from its Users.

Types of Data collected:
Among the types of Personal Data that this Application collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookies, Usage Data and email address.
Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection.
The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Application.
Any use of Cookies - or of other tracking tools - by this Application or by the owners of third party services used by this Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.
Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Application to provide its services.
Users are responsible for any Personal Data of third parties obtained, published or shared through this Application and confirm that they have the third party\'s consent to provide the Data to the Owner.
Mode and place of processing the Data
Methods of processing
The Data Controller processes the Data of Users in a proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Data Controller, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of the site (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Data Controller at any time.
Place
The Data is processed at the Data Controller\'s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved with the processing are located. For further information, please contact the Data Controller.
Retention time
The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request that the Data Controller suspend or remove the data.
The use of the collected Data
The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Access to third party accounts, Analytics, Advertising, Contacting the User and Platform services and hosting.
The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document.
Facebook permissions asked by this Application
This Application may ask for some Facebook permissions allowing it to perform actions with the User\'s Facebook account and to retrieve information, including Personal Data, from it.
For more information about the following permissions, refer to the Facebook permissions documentation and to the Facebook privacy policy.
The permissions asked are the following:
Basic information
By default, this includes certain User’s Data such as id, name, picture, gender, and their locale. Certain connections of the User, such as the Friends, are also available. If the User has made more of their Data public, more information will be available.
Status Updates
Update the User\'s status.
Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data
Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
Advertising
This type of service allows User Data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on this Application, possibly based on User interests.
This does not mean that all Personal Data are used for this purpose. Information and conditions of use are shown below.
Some of the services listed below may use Cookies to identify Users or they may use the behavioral retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the User’s interests and behavior, including those detected outside this Application. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services.
Google AdSense (Google Inc.)
Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of this Application and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.
Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: US – Privacy Policy – Opt Out
AdMob (AdMob Google Inc.)
AdMob is an advertising service provided by AdMob Google Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: US – Privacy Policy
StartApp (StartApp, Inc.)
StartApp is an advertising service provided by StartApp, Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: US – Privacy Policy
Access to third party accounts
This type of service allows this Application to access Data from your account on a third party service and perform actions with it.
These services are not activated automatically, but require explicit authorization by the User.
Facebook account access (This Application)
This service allows this Application to connect with the User\'s account on the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook, Inc.
Permissions asked: Status Updates.
Place of processing: US – Privacy Policy
Analytics
The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.
Google Analytics (Google Inc.)
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: US – Privacy Policy – Opt Out
Platform services and hosting
These services have the purpose of hosting and running key components of this Application, therefore allowing the provision of this Application from within a unified platform. Such platforms provide a wide range of tools to the Owner – e.g. analytics, user registration, commenting, database management, e-commerce, payment processing – that imply the collection and handling of Personal Data. Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored.
Blogger (Google Inc.)
Blogger is a platform provided by Google Inc. that allows the Owner to build, run and host this Application.
Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
Place of processing: USA – Privacy Policy
Push notifications
This Application may send push notifications to the User.
Contacting the User
Contact form (This Application)
By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes this Application to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.
Personal Data collected: email address.


Additional information about Data collection and processing
Legal action
The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Application or the related services.
The User declares to be aware that the Data Controller may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.
Additional information about User's Personal Data
In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Application may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.
System logs and maintenance
For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address).
Information not contained in this policy
More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.
The rights of Users
Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above.
This Application does not support “Do Not Track” requests.
To determine whether any of the third party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Application and can request that the Data Controller remove the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users.
Information about this privacy policy
The Data Controller is responsible for this privacy policy, prepared starting from the modules provided by Iubenda and hosted on Iubenda's servers.

Definitions and legal references
Personal Data (or Data)
Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.
Usage Data
Information collected automatically from this Application (or third party services employed in this Application), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Application, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment.
User
The individual using this Application, which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refers.
Data Subject
The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.
Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)
The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization authorized by the Data Controller to process the Personal Data in compliance with this privacy policy.
Data Controller (or Owner)
The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Application. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Application.
This Application
The hardware or software tool by which the Personal Data of the User is collected.
Cookies
Small piece of data stored in the User's device.
Legal information
Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies.
This privacy policy relates solely to this Application.</string>
    <string name="game_guide">Kids register for Roblox with their birth date. It’s important for kids to enter their correct birth date because Roblox has default security and privacy settings that vary, based on a player’s age.
You can check the age bracket of your child’s account by looking in the upper-right corner of the navigation bar, where it will read “13+” or less then 13,” depending on the date of birth given when the account was opened. If your child has previously set up an account incorrectly with an age of 13+, it’s simple to change the child’s age to less then 13 in the account settings section.
All Roblox games feature basic security and privacy measures. All user-uploaded images are reviewed by human moderators for inappropriate content before being posted, and there are filters that weed out bad words and other problematic language. Players age 13 and older can see and say more words and phrases than younger players, but inappropriate chat and sharing personal information (including phone numbers and addresses) are restricted regardless of age. Links to YouTube channels and social media usernames can be shared by players 13 and older.  While the imagery on Roblox has a blocky, digitized look, parents should be aware that some of the user-generated games on Roblox may include themes and/or imagery that may be too intense for young or sensitive players.</string>


    <string name="squad_team">How to Play Squads and Duos in Fortnite Battle Royale
To play as a pair or a squad of up to four, start up Fortnite Battle Royale as usual -- until you reach the gameplay menu. You\'ll then cycle through the available modes to find the Duo and Squad options using Square (PS4), X (Xbox One), or the keypad (PC) depending on the platform you’re playing on. From there, you can invite friends to play with you or you can auto-fill the slots with random players.
To invite your friends into Duos and Squads, select the empty slot and scroll through your friends list to send them an invite. In Fortnite Battle Royale, the Squad, Duo, and normal modes are separated so you can’t steamroll lone players as a group of four.
Why Play as a Squad or Duo?
Obviously, it benefits you to have another set of eyes (or three) watching your back while you're looting an area. It also helps that your teammates can revive you if you need it. </string>


    <string name="tips">They say the best things in life are free and that mostly applies to the life of a Roblox player as well. All of the best games are free-to-play without any major strings attached and you aren’t required to spend any real money to enjoy most of the content on Roblox. But if you do want to drop a few bucks here and there or subscribe to The Builders Club, you’re gonna need to know what Robux are and how they work.

Just like you need cash in real life to buy things and get by, most people are going to need some Robux to enjoy Roblox to the fullest. While the vast majority of Roblox can be accessed without spending any real money on Robux at all, there are some aspects of the game that you need Robux to see and other parts that are enhanced by the use of Robux.</string>


    <string name="tricks">How Do Robux Work?
Think of Robux as like a new type of currency. When you visit another country you’ve got to transfer your funds to the local currency, such as dollars to pounds when going from the US to the UK, and Robux are the same — except you’re swapping your dollars for Robux. It’s just a digital currency. Although, much like Monopoly money, Robux don’t have any real cash value in and of themselves.
At any time during Roblox you can visit the Buy Robux page to make a direct purchase. Spending $4.95 will grant you 400 Robux (R$) and spending $9.95 will grant you R$800. Naturally, the more you spend the better the value is. It goes all the way up to R$22,500 for $199.95.

Using Robux you can purchase limited time exclusive items, like these Sparkling Angel Wings, for your character to wear. You can also purchase Game Passes that grant in-game bonuses such as extra storage or a bigger duffel bag in the GTA-style game, Jailbreak. Then going a step even further, some games aren’t free to access like others and actually require you to spend Robux just to play the game at all, such as Welcome to Bloxburg, which costs R$25.
A lot of players put a lot of stock into how many Robux they have, sort of like a status symbol. This often leads to players feeling desperate, as if they need to find ways to get more Robux easily so that they can keep up with others. Just remember that almost everything in Roblox is free and you can have fun without ever spending money.
Avoiding Robux Scams
That being said, it’s true that Robux are what make the world of Roblox go round. And because they’re so valuable and important a lot of people will try and trick you with scams. If you ever see anything claiming to be giving out free Robux just for playing the game or if someone asks you for your information in exchange for Robux, it’s a scam and you shouldn’t trust it.

For more detailed information about avoiding Robux scams in Roblox, we’ve got you covered. Be careful out there!</string>


    <string name="vbucks">Bangladesh Railway will start selling advance train tickets on August 8 for Eid-ul-Azha travel, reports UNB. At a Dhaka Railway Bhaban press briefing on Thursday, Railways Minister Mazibul Hoque said tickets for travel on August 17, 18, 19, 20 and 21 will be available on August 8, 9, 10, 11 and 12 respectively. Tickets for the Eid-ul-Azha holiday return journeys on August 24, 25,26,27 and 28, will be available on August 15 16, 17, 18 and 19, he said. Ticket sales will begin at 8am and each passenger will be able to buy a maximum of four tickets. Nine sets of special trains for inbound and outbound travel will run on various routes on the occasion of Eid</string>
    <string name="vbucks_title">VBucks</string>
    <string name="tricks_title">Tricks</string>
    <string name="tips_title">Tips</string>
    <string name="squad_team_title">Squad and Team</string>
    <string name="game_guide_title">Robux Guide</string>
    <string name="title_activity_master">MasterActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="first_description"><pre>as a clash royale gamer, you have taken the
right decision to download this app you know why ?
before continuing take the time to give us 5 stars and a good Review
PLEASE PRESS THE BUTTON BELOW</pre></string>
    <string name="second_page">The most annoying problem when playing CR is that you are out of stock
of gems and gold which is sucks.
your preoccupation will disappear instantly unless you have gems and gold in unlimited
amonts.
Do not worry again! you can use this way without losing much time. lots $$$ and a lot of energy</string>
    <string name="third_page_first_paragraph">Prepare for victory in your battle because Here you will get easy free gems for clash royale
without much effort
without buying
without a long wait
 All you will get in a short time</string>
    <string name="third_page_second_paragraph">Get Clash Royal mods with features unlimiteds gems, golds and some interesting features please press the open button</string>
    <string name="fourth_page">Open the chest quickly or exchange with gold to upgrade the card using unlimited gems
to get free gems and gold to clash the kingdom quickly you can go to the next page.
Remember, this is a secret trick
if you want, you can try this trick</string>
</resources>
